/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368bc00c817f0398fab14b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-PGDM-a-good-option-for-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Post Graduation diploma Management (PGDM) is closely related to Industry practices and trends. PGDM course is offered by autonomous institutes which are not affiliated with any university.Hence the curriculum is updated frequently as per the changing business trends. The students learn the new and ongoing concepts of entrepreneurship. PGDM course enhances the communication and interpersonal skills of the students.The Indian education system does not focus more on communication skills right through school life. we are country of many children are not encouraged to be opinionated. We are hard wired like that parents and teacher focus more on grades. However a PGDM program develop decision making skills and analytical thinking in every students. PGDM program prepares the students for the forth Continue Reading Post Graduation diploma Management (PGDM) is closely related to Industry practices and trends. PGDM course is offered by autonomous institutes which are not affiliated with any university.Hence the curriculum is updated frequently as per the changing business trends. The students learn the new and ongoing concepts of entrepreneurship. PGDM course enhances the communication and interpersonal skills of the students.The Indian education system does not focus more on communication skills right through school life. we are country of many children are not encouraged to be opinionated. We are hard wired like that parents and teacher focus more on grades. However a PGDM program develop decision making skills and analytical thinking in every students. PGDM program prepares the students for the forth Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:24:15.774Z"),
    "question" : "Is PGDM a good option for a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368bd20c817f0398fab169"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-suggestions-after-PGDM?-",
    "answer" : "The PGDM is not just a plain course, it polishes and grooms your overall personality starting from sharpening your interpersonal effectiveness to honing your hidden skills. Moreover, one learns better presentation skills, faces real-time business scenarios and develops a problem-solving attitude. After successful completion, students can even look forward to campus placements with impressive packages by good and reputed companies. Here are some career options you can consider after pursuing the course. Get a chance to join the Private Sector: If you look forward to growth-oriented and lucrative jobs then the private sector is all there to fulfill your dreams after PGDM. Join big conglomerates and growing concerns as business manager, management trainee, finance executive, marketing assistanContinue Reading The PGDM is not just a plain course, it polishes and grooms your overall personality starting from sharpening your interpersonal effectiveness to honing your hidden skills. Moreover, one learns better presentation skills, faces real-time business scenarios and develops a problem-solving attitude. After successful completion, students can even look forward to campus placements with impressive packages by good and reputed companies. Here are some career options you can consider after pursuing the course. Get a chance to join the Private Sector: If you look forward to growth-oriented and lucrative jobs then the private sector is all there to fulfill your dreams after PGDM. Join big conglomerates and growing concerns as business manager, management trainee, finance executive, marketing assistanContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:24:34.774Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career suggestions after PGDM? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368be80c817f0398fab189"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-MBA-and-PGDM-courses-in-terms-of-career-progress-and-also-the-value-in-India-compared-to-Canada?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the difference between MBA and PGDM courses in terms of career progress and also the value in India compared to Canada?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:24:56.499Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between MBA and PGDM courses in terms of career progress and also the value in India compared to Canada? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368c100c817f0398fab212"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-PGDM-in-research-and-business-analytics-have-good-future-prospects?-",
    "answer" : "Business analytics is one of the most budding domains in the modern world and many students are showing their interest to pursue their career and studies in this field. Business analytics is the study of data of an organization by giving importance to statistical analysis. A business analyst helps an organization to make data-driven decisions and analyses the data to turn it into useful information. A business analyst uses Big Data to find patterns and anomalies which help an enterprise to solve a particular problem. Business analysts have an amazing future prospect. In the past recent years, the demand for business and data analysts have drastically increased, and every organization is looking for such candidates who are very good with analytics. A PGDM course can propel your career to the Continue Reading Business analytics is one of the most budding domains in the modern world and many students are showing their interest to pursue their career and studies in this field. Business analytics is the study of data of an organization by giving importance to statistical analysis. A business analyst helps an organization to make data-driven decisions and analyses the data to turn it into useful information. A business analyst uses Big Data to find patterns and anomalies which help an enterprise to solve a particular problem. Business analysts have an amazing future prospect. In the past recent years, the demand for business and data analysts have drastically increased, and every organization is looking for such candidates who are very good with analytics. A PGDM course can propel your career to the Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:25:36.987Z"),
    "question" : "Does PGDM in research and business analytics have good future prospects? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368c300c817f0398fab28f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-course-should-I-opt-finance-or-marketing-in-PGDM?-",
    "answer" : "PGDM degree with dual specialisation solves this demand-supply gap. One of the most popular dual specialisation is Marketing and Finance. Both specialisations are integral part of the industry. Many Institutes like Global Institute of Business School (GIBS) Bangalore, Christ University, Amity University etc.. provides PGDM in Dual Slecialisations. PGDM in Finance An PGDM program with a concentration in finance prepares graduates to make financial decisions for a variety of businesses and organizations. PGDM programs include finance courses that teach students how to acquire, manage and distribute funds in a business setting. Typical courses include marketing, international business and finance, budgeting, financial accounting, data analysis and economics. Students can choose to concentrate in Continue Reading PGDM degree with dual specialisation solves this demand-supply gap. One of the most popular dual specialisation is Marketing and Finance. Both specialisations are integral part of the industry. Many Institutes like Global Institute of Business School (GIBS) Bangalore, Christ University, Amity University etc.. provides PGDM in Dual Slecialisations. PGDM in Finance An PGDM program with a concentration in finance prepares graduates to make financial decisions for a variety of businesses and organizations. PGDM programs include finance courses that teach students how to acquire, manage and distribute funds in a business setting. Typical courses include marketing, international business and finance, budgeting, financial accounting, data analysis and economics. Students can choose to concentrate in Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:26:08.811Z"),
    "question" : "What course should I opt finance or marketing in PGDM? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368c4b0c817f0398fab2ac"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-PGDM-in-Data-Science-as-a-career-option?-",
    "answer" : "PGDM stands for Post Graduate Diploma in Management. It is a two-year full-time management course offered by many institutes in India. This course can be divided into four or six semesters depending upon the different institutes and their curriculum. The institutes, running PGDM courses in India are approved by AICTE, under the Ministry of HRD, Government of India. The course structure and subjects of PGDM is almost similar to an MBA. The only difference between them is that an MBA provides a degree while PGDM is a Post Graduate Diploma. PGDM programs may not be affiliated with any university so it should not be considered as a degree course. Following is a list of some most common subjects in PGDM across all institutes in India. MarketingHuman resourcesFinanceAccountingOperations managementIContinue Reading PGDM stands for Post Graduate Diploma in Management. It is a two-year full-time management course offered by many institutes in India. This course can be divided into four or six semesters depending upon the different institutes and their curriculum. The institutes, running PGDM courses in India are approved by AICTE, under the Ministry of HRD, Government of India. The course structure and subjects of PGDM is almost similar to an MBA. The only difference between them is that an MBA provides a degree while PGDM is a Post Graduate Diploma. PGDM programs may not be affiliated with any university so it should not be considered as a degree course. Following is a list of some most common subjects in PGDM across all institutes in India. MarketingHuman resourcesFinanceAccountingOperations managementIContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:26:35.953Z"),
    "question" : "How good is PGDM in Data Science as a career option? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368c650c817f0398fab31d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Marketing-Hr-a-dual-specialization-good-career-option-in-PGDM-course?-",
    "answer" : "I had opted for Marketing and HR specializations in PGDM. While Dual specialization helps during interview process, to appear for jobs under both categories; but, once you are in a job it is difficult to change career options (but definitely definitely possible). They say career is a marathon not a sprint. So, it is in your best interests to carefully select the areas you wish to specialize. I understand that not many companies may turn up to hire for Marketing profiles which interests you (or your area of interest). Then, if your aim is to secure a job, go for specializations which will help you earn your bread. You can later try moving across teams within the company. Also, carefully select your electives which are complimentary. For example, knowledge about Branding / Advertising helps HR Continue Reading I had opted for Marketing and HR specializations in PGDM. While Dual specialization helps during interview process, to appear for jobs under both categories; but, once you are in a job it is difficult to change career options (but definitely definitely possible). They say career is a marathon not a sprint. So, it is in your best interests to carefully select the areas you wish to specialize. I understand that not many companies may turn up to hire for Marketing profiles which interests you (or your area of interest). Then, if your aim is to secure a job, go for specializations which will help you earn your bread. You can later try moving across teams within the company. Also, carefully select your electives which are complimentary. For example, knowledge about Branding / Advertising helps HR Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:27:01.192Z"),
    "question" : "Is Marketing-Hr a dual specialization good career option in PGDM course? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368c800c817f0398fab331"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-will-be-the-effect-of-a-3-year-gap-before-an-MBA-or-a-PGDM-on-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:27:28.910Z"),
    "question" : "What will be the effect of a 3-year gap before an MBA or a PGDM on a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368cb20c817f0398fab3bf"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-a-PGDM-in-risk-management-have-a-good-career?-",
    "answer" : "GRMI Offers a Specialised Post Graduate Diploma in Risk Management — 800 hrs of practical case study based learning from a mix of Corporate and Academia Professionals. The curriculum has a strong component of real-life case studies that make the experience significantly more interesting and experiential than classroom learning. The curriculum and learning experience are co-created with the key stakeholders of the ecosystem of risk – leading corporates and risk consulting firms. This ensures the relevance and acceptance of both the curriculum and the qualification. Have a look at their Placements and Internship Update for PGDRM 2017-18 in PwC, Grant Thorton, TPG Capital, PepsiCo, Startup-o, EnY, Eicher Motors, HT Media etc. Internships & Pre-Placement opportunities This has link to profiles o Continue Reading GRMI Offers a Specialised Post Graduate Diploma in Risk Management — 800 hrs of practical case study based learning from a mix of Corporate and Academia Professionals. The curriculum has a strong component of real-life case studies that make the experience significantly more interesting and experiential than classroom learning. The curriculum and learning experience are co-created with the key stakeholders of the ecosystem of risk – leading corporates and risk consulting firms. This ensures the relevance and acceptance of both the curriculum and the qualification. Have a look at their Placements and Internship Update for PGDRM 2017-18 in PwC, Grant Thorton, TPG Capital, PepsiCo, Startup-o, EnY, Eicher Motors, HT Media etc. Internships & Pre-Placement opportunities This has link to profiles o Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:28:18.706Z"),
    "question" : "Does a PGDM in risk management have a good career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368cc70c817f0398fab3d7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-after-a-PGDM-from-Goa-Institute-of-Management?-",
    "answer" : "Great career ahead! But it has plenty of ifs and buts. First and most important is which specialisation you choose and secondly, what are the opportunities after you pass out. The placements have been good over the years but it also has been mixed for each speacialisation. In the market, I would definitely say that GIM is viewed only as B-Grade college as it doesn't make to the top 10 or even top 20 in the league tables these days. But there are quite a few alumni who have weathered the storm and headwinds and have succeeded much more than an average A-Grade passout. Remember, it doesn't come easy. Those successful people are those who are so passionate about their job that they can swim in any waters. Success stories vary in a broad spectrum of great to ok-ish. A quick glance at this page woul Continue Reading Great career ahead! But it has plenty of ifs and buts. First and most important is which specialisation you choose and secondly, what are the opportunities after you pass out. The placements have been good over the years but it also has been mixed for each speacialisation. In the market, I would definitely say that GIM is viewed only as B-Grade college as it doesn't make to the top 10 or even top 20 in the league tables these days. But there are quite a few alumni who have weathered the storm and headwinds and have succeeded much more than an average A-Grade passout. Remember, it doesn't come easy. Those successful people are those who are so passionate about their job that they can swim in any waters. Success stories vary in a broad spectrum of great to ok-ish. A quick glance at this page woul Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:28:39.861Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career after a PGDM from Goa Institute of Management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368cdd0c817f0398fab449"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-PGDM-in-the-Indian-Institute-of-Packaging-good-for-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Hi Yes, definitely. If you are looking something different as your career option then it’s the good demanding field. As most of the company need cost effective way to transport their products worldwide. Again the program is offered by governement institution, so there is no doubt about the said program. Now again its your level of interest to get into. If you need more information kindly pm me. Good luck.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:29:01.063Z"),
    "question" : "Is PGDM in the Indian Institute of Packaging good for a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368cef0c817f0398fab455"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-has-the-Welingkar-Hybrid-PGDM-helped-you-in-your-career?-",
    "answer" : "I have no clue about this course. If it's a more recent one, consider it just another gimmick. You can't have dozens of courses in an institute and then expect the institute to provide quality education in each one of them. Getting a handful of good faculty is a task. But if you have a dozen courses in an institute, it is impossible to make all these courses to be at par. Except for the common courses, specific courses in one may work while the others may falter. In short, if you are in no hurry, AVOID.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:29:19.176Z"),
    "question" : "How has the Welingkar Hybrid PGDM helped you in your career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368d020c817f0398fab46d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-PGDM-in-Media-and-Entertainment-a-good-career-option?-",
    "answer" : "Kanchan Yadav Pgdm in Media and Entertainment: Media and Entertainment industry is rapidly growing today. This industry includes digital media, radio, print, television, live events, music and films. A Post Graduate diploma course in media and entertainment guides students to become business managers in these fields. The course includes general aspects in these industries.  Programme: The course teaches students to become successful managers in the entertainment and media industry. Students get to visit various production houses, media agencies, advertising offices and get to attend workshops. After the course, the students can become business managers with a media edge. Career Prospects: o brand marketing o content business o client servicing o consumer research o digital media o public relations o advertising o ev Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:29:38.149Z"),
    "question" : "Is PGDM in Media and Entertainment a good career option? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368d330c817f0398fab4f2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-opportunities-for-a-PGDM-Retail-Management?-",
    "answer" : "Swara Patil, studied at MITAnswered September 3, 2020 · Author has 105 answers and 29.7K answer viewsWhat are the career opportunities for a PGDM Retail Management? Swara Patil Hi, Retail marketing is among one the applications of marketing functions in the distribution of commodities to consumers. Organized retail is not only about selling goods; it includes activities of marketing like rating packing, publicity, and advertisements and showcasing a variety of products at a fair price with offers like a discount, credit. Retail Marketing provides assistance, comfort in shopping in place, or medium that is beneficial to the consumer. It provides a complete overview of the concept of visual marketing and highlights consumer relationship management, brand management, and sales management. Products are created with the aim of the consumption and satisfaction of consumers. They should reach people for whom they are expected. A retailer is the one who understands the rol Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:30:27.501Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career opportunities for a PGDM Retail Management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368d660c817f0398fab57e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-opportunities-after-studying-a-PGDM-in-human-resource-management?-",
    "answer" : "PGDM - HRM (Human Resource Management) is one of the best thing in job industry. Basically human resource is used to describe both the people who work for a company or organization and the department responsible to managing resources related to employee. Many colleges are offering PGDM - HRM The two-year Post Graduate Diploma in Management such as Lloyd business School offering the same course collaboration with Manpower.  Is Human Resource a good career to pursue ? Career option after pursuing Human Resource Management course and PGDM -HRM  HR Specialist  HR consultant HR Generalist Director HR Assistant Vice President HR Vice President HR Board of Directors Chief HR Officer",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:31:18.198Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career opportunities after studying a PGDM in human resource management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368d900c817f0398fab5af"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Will-pursuing-a-PGDM-at-IMT-Ghaziabad-though-distance-learning-be-better-for-my-career?-",
    "answer" : "IMT Ghaziabad is a good option for PGDM because it’s UGC approved, In terms of exposure IMT GHAZIABAD POST GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN MANAGEMENT (EXECUTIVE): PGDM (Executive) is specially designed for individuals taking on larger critical roles in their organizations and businesses. This program differentiates itself in focusing on experiential learning through real business cases, experience sharing and, role play. The program content has been designed keeping industry insights pertaining to working executives. They need programs that provide the right flexibility to enable them to pursue their careers and education together. At the same time program should ensure a very high-quality experience. To ensure competency building inspecific domains the PGEM has been designed in such a fashion that in  Continue Reading IMT Ghaziabad is a good option for PGDM because it’s UGC approved, In terms of exposure IMT GHAZIABAD POST GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN MANAGEMENT (EXECUTIVE): PGDM (Executive) is specially designed for individuals taking on larger critical roles in their organizations and businesses. This program differentiates itself in focusing on experiential learning through real business cases, experience sharing and, role play. The program content has been designed keeping industry insights pertaining to working executives. They need programs that provide the right flexibility to enable them to pursue their careers and education together. At the same time program should ensure a very high-quality experience. To ensure competency building inspecific domains the PGEM has been designed in such a fashion that in  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:32:00.162Z"),
    "question" : "Will pursuing a PGDM at IMT Ghaziabad though distance learning be better for my career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368daa0c817f0398fab61b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-Great-Lakes-Pgpm-Chennai-to-pursue-a-career-in-Finance?-",
    "answer" : "The quality of Finance professors at Great Lakes is splendid. You get some of the best in class professors to teach you the Frameworks of Finance. Even though, I didn’t major in Finance, I still remember the great classes we had in the likes of Financial Management or Financial Modelling. However when you choose PGPM, remember that you have a very short time span before you land up in Placement Interviews. By the time, you would still be halfway through the course and you would have learnt only the basics of Finance. It is due to this major factor, many of the hardcore Finance companies feel that 1 Year courses are not suitable for taking employees in Finance domain. If you have a solid work experience in Finance prior to MBA, it might work better. That being said, we have some great Alumni Continue Reading The quality of Finance professors at Great Lakes is splendid. You get some of the best in class professors to teach you the Frameworks of Finance. Even though, I didn’t major in Finance, I still remember the great classes we had in the likes of Financial Management or Financial Modelling. However when you choose PGPM, remember that you have a very short time span before you land up in Placement Interviews. By the time, you would still be halfway through the course and you would have learnt only the basics of Finance. It is due to this major factor, many of the hardcore Finance companies feel that 1 Year courses are not suitable for taking employees in Finance domain. If you have a solid work experience in Finance prior to MBA, it might work better. That being said, we have some great Alumni Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:32:26.627Z"),
    "question" : "How good is Great Lakes Pgpm Chennai to pursue a career in Finance? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368dc30c817f0398fab63d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-private-MBA-or-PGDM-college-is-the-best-in-terms-of-career-and-placement?-",
    "answer" : "Which private MBA or PGDM college is the best in terms of career and placement? Since there are over 4400 management colleges in India, choosing the one which offers the best career and placement is no cakewalk. To help you out, I have created a list of three private MBA & PGDM colleges that have a reputation for having the most desirable placement records. ASM's IBMR Pune - Institute of Business Management and ResearchXavier School of Management (XLRI), JamshedpurSP Jain Institute of Management and Research, MumbaiAll of these colleges are known to offer students excellent placement opportunities. Almost all of them provide 100 percent placement assurance for summer internships and final campus recruitment. Along with a good placement record, these colleges have a strong legacy, experienced Continue Reading Which private MBA or PGDM college is the best in terms of career and placement? Since there are over 4400 management colleges in India, choosing the one which offers the best career and placement is no cakewalk. To help you out, I have created a list of three private MBA & PGDM colleges that have a reputation for having the most desirable placement records. ASM's IBMR Pune - Institute of Business Management and ResearchXavier School of Management (XLRI), JamshedpurSP Jain Institute of Management and Research, MumbaiAll of these colleges are known to offer students excellent placement opportunities. Almost all of them provide 100 percent placement assurance for summer internships and final campus recruitment. Along with a good placement record, these colleges have a strong legacy, experienced Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:32:51.319Z"),
    "question" : "Which private MBA or PGDM college is the best in terms of career and placement? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368e010c817f0398fab6d4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Will-GCT-be-a-good-career-for-pursuing-PGDM?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Will pursuing a PGDM at IMT Ghaziabad though distance learning be better for my career?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:33:53.447Z"),
    "question" : "Will GCT be a good career for pursuing PGDM? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368e270c817f0398fab74e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-PGDM-in-Finance-a-good-career-option?-",
    "answer" : "Finance is always considered as the complicated part and so it requires lots of specialization and professional skills. For running a smooth business, organizations are likely to hire finance PGDM students. The scope of PGDM in finance is huge these days. A PGDM Finance degree offers a much wider scope of career enhancement and prospects compared to other accounting degrees, as it covers various aspects of accounting and managing finance like investments, securities, business, banking and risk management.PGDM finance helps organization to manage the finances of the company effectively.Market analysis and cash management skills are two important skills to get good jobs in finance sector. Financial companies are likely to hire highly skilled professionals for their financial activities and s Continue Reading Finance is always considered as the complicated part and so it requires lots of specialization and professional skills. For running a smooth business, organizations are likely to hire finance PGDM students. The scope of PGDM in finance is huge these days. A PGDM Finance degree offers a much wider scope of career enhancement and prospects compared to other accounting degrees, as it covers various aspects of accounting and managing finance like investments, securities, business, banking and risk management.PGDM finance helps organization to manage the finances of the company effectively.Market analysis and cash management skills are two important skills to get good jobs in finance sector. Financial companies are likely to hire highly skilled professionals for their financial activities and s Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:34:31.372Z"),
    "question" : "Is PGDM in Finance a good career option? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368e620c817f0398fab7fa"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-differences-between-the-career-opportunities-for-a-PGDM-student-and-an-MBA?-",
    "answer" : "There are no such differences in the career opportunities for a PDGM and an MBA. Companies want people with a required skillset and if you have that skill set, company will take you. I am from KJ Somaiya institute of management studies and research (simsr), mumbai . In my college we have both PGDM and MMS course. All students from these courses get an equal opportunity to perform and showcase their skills to the companies. To sum up, there is no difference in career opportunities for these students doing a pgdm and an mba course Khan Mohammad Amir",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:35:30.765Z"),
    "question" : "What are the differences between the career opportunities for a PGDM student and an MBA? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368e9a0c817f0398fab899"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-PGDM-in-IB-good-for-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "It depends. Can I ask you more details on grades and graduation. You may write to me for professional career advise. Regards",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:36:26.816Z"),
    "question" : "Is a PGDM in IB good for a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368eb30c817f0398fab8bc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-opportunities-in-US-for-an-Indian-PGDM?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:36:51.570Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career opportunities in US for an Indian PGDM? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368f140c817f0398fab9d5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-PGDM-career-path-for-the-coming-years?-",
    "answer" : "PGDM is highly acceptable and carries more value than MBA in our country only. If we plan to to move abroad PGDM is certainly considered as a valuable management program awarded by Central Government of India but it is considered as diploma in management studies. So in countries like Australia, United States of America a candidate cannot pursue P.HD post PGDM from India. So it is our country which gives more value to PGDM then MBA because of updated course curriculum and corporate exposure. 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:38:28.245Z"),
    "question" : "What is the PGDM career path for the coming years? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368f2e0c817f0398fab9f8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-options-at-the-entry-level-after-a-PGDM-in-supply-chain-and-logistics-management?-",
    "answer" : "Supply chain management is an integral part of every organization to ensure maximum efficiency of production and supply. Once you complete a PGDM in supply chain and logistics management, you can choose from different entry-level job profiles mentioned below: Supply Chain CoordinatorAssistant Supply Chain ManagerLogistics CoordinatorDistribution ManagerIndustry AnalystJunior Project ManagerProcurement AnalystDepending on the company you work for, the job responsibilities will vary for every role. One of the most secure ways to grab a good opportunity in this industry is through college placement drives. This will help you learn about your potential employers and what they are expecting from supply chain management graduates. All of this information will eventually help you make informed dec Continue Reading Supply chain management is an integral part of every organization to ensure maximum efficiency of production and supply. Once you complete a PGDM in supply chain and logistics management, you can choose from different entry-level job profiles mentioned below: Supply Chain CoordinatorAssistant Supply Chain ManagerLogistics CoordinatorDistribution ManagerIndustry AnalystJunior Project ManagerProcurement AnalystDepending on the company you work for, the job responsibilities will vary for every role. One of the most secure ways to grab a good opportunity in this industry is through college placement drives. This will help you learn about your potential employers and what they are expecting from supply chain management graduates. All of this information will eventually help you make informed dec Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:38:54.612Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career options at the entry level after a PGDM in supply chain and logistics management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368f6c0c817f0398faba99"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-options-after-PGDM-in-Global?-",
    "answer" : "Vinod Kumar Saini",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:39:56.599Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career options after PGDM in Global? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60368fa40c817f0398fabb2c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-opportunities-after-a-PGDM-in-service-management?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:40:52.754Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career opportunities after a PGDM in service management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036903f0c817f0398fabcdd"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-Garware-Institute-of-Career-Education-and-Development-Mumbai-for-a-PGDM?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the difference between a PGDM and an MBA course in the same college?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:43:27.344Z"),
    "question" : "How is Garware Institute of Career Education and Development Mumbai for a PGDM? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603690550c817f0398fabd08"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-Symbiosis-Pune-PGDM-boost-my-career?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:43:49.426Z"),
    "question" : "How does Symbiosis Pune PGDM boost my career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036909c0c817f0398fabdb9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-tips-and-tricks-in-pursuing-PGDM-in-finance-ie-certifications-which-help-in-career-prospect?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:45:00.050Z"),
    "question" : "What are the tips and tricks in pursuing PGDM in finance ie certifications which help in career prospect? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603690ca0c817f0398fabe47"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Career-advice?-I-want-to-approach-investment-banking-firms-in-US-UK-or-Germany-for-a-placement-after-my-PGDM-in-finance-from-all-india-management-association-how-can-I-do-it?-Need-help?-",
    "answer" : "This is just my observation from my perch in the cockpit. I think it’s probably harder in the long run. First, in the U.S. it’s probably easier to be hired once you’ve reached the minimum requirements that the airline has established. There is a long history of discrimination against women and the cor (more)",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:45:46.448Z"),
    "question" : "Is it easy to become a female commercial pilot? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603690e10c817f0398fabebb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-you-boost-your-career-in-PGDM-operations?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:46:09.103Z"),
    "question" : "How can you boost your career in PGDM operations? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603690f70c817f0398fabed3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-1-year-PGDM-in-project-management-and-1-year-PGDM-in-international-business-enough-in-Canada-for-starting-a-career-there?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:46:31.136Z"),
    "question" : "Is 1 year PGDM in project management and 1 year PGDM in international business enough in Canada for starting a career there? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036912a0c817f0398fabf66"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-tangible-advantage-in-career-after-doing-PGDM-Hybrid-program-from-Wellingkars?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Ankit Sharma",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:47:22.443Z"),
    "question" : "What is the tangible advantage in career after doing PGDM Hybrid program from Wellingkars? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603691650c817f0398fac007"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-good-to-start-a-career-in-agricultural-value-chain-finance-as-a-PGDM-agribusiness-graduate?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Saksham Kaparwan 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:48:21.553Z"),
    "question" : "Is it good to start a career in agricultural value chain finance as a PGDM agribusiness graduate? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603691850c817f0398fac038"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-good-part-time-colleges-offering-PGDM-in-operation-management-in-Bangalore-and-what’s-the-career-scope-after-completion?-",
    "answer" : "Hi As you want to do PGDM course so here I am suggesting you the Evening Colleges that offer PGDM course in Bangalore List of Colleges offer PGDM in Bangalore- The Institute of Chartered Financial Analysts of India Mahatma Gandhi Road, BangaloreMBA (Sectorial) in Hospital, Pharma and Telecom Management - 2 Years Correspondence , Post Graduate DegreeUGC Recognised Alliance School of Business - Alliance UniversityAnekal, BangaloreExecutive Post Graduate Diploma in Management (Weekends') - 16 Months Part Time , Post Graduate DiplomaUGC Recognised Tasmac Business SchoolKudalu Gate, BangaloreMaster of Business Administration - 2 Years , Part Time , Post Graduate DegreeAffiliated to University of Wales Symbiosis Institute of Business ManagementHosur Road, Bangalore\tPGDM in Financial Management - 1 Year , Part Time , Post Graduate DiplomaAICTE Approved St. Joseph's College of CommerceBrigade Road, BangalorePost Graduate Diploma in Business Administration - 1 Year , Part Time Post Graduate DiplomaAffiliated to Bangalore University Aptech Aviation and Hospitality Academy Bangalore Jayanagar, Bangalore\tMaster of Business Administration in Aviation - 2 Years , Part TimePost Graduate DegreeAffiliated to Mahatma Gandhi University (MGU) Indian Institute of Materials Management M. G. Road, Bangalore\tMBA (Materials Management) - 2 Years , Part Time , Post Graduate DegreeUGC Recognised , DEC Approved , Affiliated to MP Bhoj (0pen) University, Gupta College of Management and Technology Banashankari, Bangalore\tExecutive Masters in Business Administration- Corporate (MBA) weekend - 1 Year, Part Time , Post Graduate DegreeAffiliated to International American University NIIT Imperia Centre for Advanced Learning Bangalore, Jayanagar, Bangalore\tPost Graduate Diploma In International Business Strategy - 1 Year, Part Time , Post Graduate DiplomaAffiliated to Deemed University MIIT Software Training Institute BTM 2nd Stage, Bangalore\tHuman Resource mangement (core H R) - 1 Month\t, Part Time , Post Graduate Degree Vasavi Institute of Management & Advanced Studies Banashankari, Bangalore\tMaster of Business Administration - 2 Years , Part Time , Post Graduate DegreeUGC Recognised , Affiliated to Manonmaniam Sundaranar University Cygmax Institute of Management StudiesBangaloreMBAPlus Programme (Week end Programme) - 2 Years , Part Time , Post Graduate Degree Singapore Human Resourses Institute Mallathalli, Bangalore\tPost Graduate Diploma in Management-Global Business Administration - 2 Years, Part Time , Post Graduate DiplomaAffiliated to Singapore Human Resources Institute EduSpire Services Pvt Ltd Bangalore\tMaster of Business Administration (MBA) - 2 Years , Part Time , Post Graduate Degree",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:48:53.682Z"),
    "question" : "What are the good part time colleges offering PGDM in operation management in Bangalore and what’s the career scope after completion? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603691cb0c817f0398fac142"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Will-I-be-considered-too-old-to-pursue-PGDM-from-IIMs-at-the-age-of-28-for-a-career-switch?-",
    "answer" : "You are just 28 and you are so worried ? I am 36 and still eagerly and passionately studying to complete my Fellow in management.  Career switch should be smart and should be  made with due preparation.  Your experience should be a value add and not get wasted is the only thing you should keep in your mind... Deepak Raj",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:50:03.056Z"),
    "question" : "Will I be considered too old to pursue PGDM from IIMs at the age of 28 for a career switch? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603691f70c817f0398fac196"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-flourish-a-business-career-as-a-PGDM-graduate?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:50:47.024Z"),
    "question" : "How do I flourish a business career as a PGDM graduate? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036928b0c817f0398fac36e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-options-are-open-to-one-after-doing-a-PGDM-and-a-BA-in-HM?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:53:15.884Z"),
    "question" : "What career options are open to one after doing a PGDM and a BA in HM? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603692a00c817f0398fac393"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-opportunities-in-marketing-and-information-systems-in-PGDM-as-a-dual-specialization?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:53:36.455Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career opportunities in marketing and information systems in PGDM as a dual specialization? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603692d40c817f0398fac434"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-career-aspects-of-doing-an-MSc-in-finance-after-a-PGDM-in-finance-and-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:54:28.830Z"),
    "question" : "What are career aspects of doing an MSc in finance after a PGDM in finance and engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603692fd0c817f0398fac4cc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-have-a-career-in-marketing-if-I-do-PGDM-HRM-from-IMI-Delhi?-",
    "answer" : "Bikash Pratap Singh Sherry Singh Ankit Dhir",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:55:09.878Z"),
    "question" : "Can I have a career in marketing if I do PGDM-HRM from IMI-Delhi? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036936c0c817f0398fac5cb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-your-opinions-on-pursuing-a-PGDM-in-Canada-in-career-prospects?-",
    "answer" : "Opting a PGDM in Canada.There are better options concerning Management education in Singapore,US etc. But if you are thinking that a diploma in management from Canada would help you in settelment and a descent job there in Canada.Then its 50–50 chances. But if you had done bachelors and some other diploma or degree from their that would have helped you.Dont worry bro,dont loose hope,consult a good immigration consultant,a real good one.may be telephonically and plan your future accordingly.but dont call just one consultant.you may visit or call one or two local consultants and some other good immigration consultants in new delhi.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:57:00.179Z"),
    "question" : "What are your opinions on pursuing a PGDM in Canada in career prospects? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603693840c817f0398fac644"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-pursue-PGDIE-in-NITIE-Mumbai-or-PGDM-in-IIMs-to-grow-a-career-in-Automotive-sector?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:57:24.699Z"),
    "question" : "Should I pursue PGDIE in NITIE Mumbai or PGDM in IIMs to grow a career in Automotive sector? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036939b0c817f0398fac673"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-has-an-executive-PGDM-from-IMT-CDL-impacted-your-career?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:57:47.036Z"),
    "question" : "How has an executive PGDM from IMT CDL impacted your career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603693f20c817f0398fac798"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-would-be-the-career-options-after-completing-a-PGDM-in-travel-and-tourism-management?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are career options in travel and tourism management?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:59:14.847Z"),
    "question" : "What would be the career options after completing a PGDM in travel and tourism management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603694120c817f0398fac7d3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-will-a-distance-MBA-while-working-in-an-IT-company-help-in-my-career-growth?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers C.J. Liu 2",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T17:59:46.963Z"),
    "question" : "How will a distance MBA while working in an IT company help in my career growth? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036944c0c817f0398fac87a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-program-would-be-better-between-IMT-Ghaziabad-Dual-country-profram-and-Great-Lakes-PGDM-for-a-career-in-marketing?-",
    "answer" : "Rishabh G",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:00:44.580Z"),
    "question" : "Which program would be better between IMT Ghaziabad Dual country profram and Great Lakes PGDM for a career in marketing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603694ab0c817f0398fac9b3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-knowledge-and-career-oriented-is-MICA-University-in-PGDM-Communications-Management?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:02:19.177Z"),
    "question" : "How knowledge and career oriented is MICA University in PGDM-Communications Management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603694c70c817f0398fac9e7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-options-available-for-a-PGDM-in-finance-who-completes-a-certification-in-financial-data-analytics?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:02:47.105Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career options available for a PGDM in finance who completes a certification in financial data analytics? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603695050c817f0398faca9b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-career-should-I-choose-having-a-computer-engineering-and-PGDM-in-marketing?-",
    "answer" : "This is a vey vague question. Because you have not listed your actual interests and skills sets which includes both interpersonal skills and technical skills, it is almost impossible to tell you an optmial career choice. We should stop following ‘One size, fits all' approach. We should stop following the ‘popular' choices and start focusing on where our interest are and what we are good at. If you can't figure it out yourself through self-realization, then maybe you take the help of a Career Coach like me.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:03:49.429Z"),
    "question" : "What career should I choose having a computer engineering and PGDM in marketing? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603695180c817f0398facb0b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-will-be-your-career-advice-for-someone-after-completing-a-PGDM-in-infrastructure-management?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers How is MBA infrastructure management in symbiosis? Are the placements guaranteed? How is the job profile after completion of the course? DISCLAIMER: ALL THE INFORMATION BELOW IS AS ACCURATE AS IT CAN BE AND IS SOURCED FROM A PERSON WHO HAS BEEN A STUDENT THERE, A VERY VERY DEAR FRIEND OF MINETrue, like any MBA course, it is comprehensive, gruelling and toll-taking. BUT..these are the reasons why it is honestly not worth your time or your money-1.      General issues with the institute (not exactly pertaining to IM)a.      So at SCMHRD, you see a lot of activities, lot of buzz, competitions, winning in competitions, festivities, committee work, events etc. It’s a roller coaster ride which abuts your course-curriculum and, even though tiring, it sure is exciting. The problem comes during placements. It is almost completely handled by students (YES, PEOPLE AMONG YOU WHO MAY ALSO HAVE NO EXPERIENCE WITH CORPORATES MAY BE THE Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:04:08.304Z"),
    "question" : "What will be your career advice for someone after completing a PGDM in infrastructure management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603695380c817f0398facb3b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-well-off-are-the-career-prospects-for-a-legal-professional-with-an-MBA-or-PGDM-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the job prospects after an MBA in Canada?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:04:40.955Z"),
    "question" : "How well off are the career prospects for a legal professional with an MBA or PGDM in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603695750c817f0398facbed"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-career-opportunities-for-PGDM-as-a-fresher-in-off-campus-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Career Opportunities for PGDM Finance, PGDM Human Resource, PGDM Marketing PGDM Finance Post Graduate Diploma Management with specialization in Finance, for students who aim to pursue management education. The two year post-graduate diploma course can be taken as an alternative course for the overrated MBA course. Students of any the stream can apply for this course. Eligibility: · 50 per cent marks in bachelor’s program · Entrance exam The course is mainly created for students who want to increase their knowledge and capabilities in the field of financial management, such as working capital management, international finance and merger acquisition among others. It makes the students aware of their duties and responsibilities towards the company as a financial manager. It also provides an overview of how to analyse cost center expenses thereby-formulating balance sheets It helps to forte the concept of maximizing profits and minimizing costs. The various PGDM Finance job types are: · Financial adviser · Financial planner · Investment banker · Equity analyst · Finance manager · Bankers Students gets an average annual PGDM salary starting from INR 2-15 lakh. Top recruiting companies are as follows: · AIG Bangalore · AMC'S · BoeingBangalore · ABBOTT · CBRE · ICICI BANK · KPMG · YES BANK · AIRTEL · TATA CAPITAL · BAJAJ CAPITAL · MTR · Accenture · TIME · 99 ACRES · CITY UNION. BANK This career option is one of the most recommended course throughout the world as it provides excellent job opportunities in various renowned organization mainly focusing on financial background. Career planning in the postgraduate includes · Asset Management · Retail Banking · Financial Advisory · Taxation · Corporate Finance · Investment Banker · Risk Management · Equity Analyst · Business Analyst etc. PGDM Human ResourceManagement Postgraduate business Course in Human Resource Management is a two year post graduate course is designed to provide eligible, competent, suitable human resource professionals with sufficient knowledge and expertise in the business. It helps in cracking some top brands placement like: · TCS · AMAZON · DR REDDY’S · DELOITTE · APOLLO · RANDSTAD · ICICI BANK · DUKES Te course is particularly created to suit the requirements of HR professionals. It is a unique long term project which results in obtaining pre-placement offers. Students are demonstrated to become the members of HR hub. Objectives of PGDM HR program: The main focus is to facilitate accelerated learning in the formulation and implementation of best practices in human resource management. To offer the experimental analysis so that students can understand the challenges faced by an HR professional better. To establish a connection between executives and HR. PGDM Marketing Postgraduate Diploma Management in Marketing is basically a two-year course designed for students and corporates in recent times. It helps in understanding the market and portfolios of product offerings. It involves: · Identifying the target market · Market observation · Products development Career options in PGDM Marketing: · Sales manager · Brand manager · Market research analysis · Public relations manager · Digital marketing Top recruiting companies include: · FLIPKART · INDIABULLS · L'OREAL INDIA · ICICI BANK · TATA MOTORS FINANCE LIMITED · AMERICAN EXPRESS · ITC · CAVINKARE · BLUE STAR · IDFC BANK · EBIX · WIPRO · AXIS BANK · MUTHOOT FINANCE Best College PGDM program: XIDAS",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:05:41.614Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best career opportunities for PGDM as a fresher in off campus in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603695910c817f0398facc73"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-certifications-that-can-help-PGDM-students-to-make-a-growth-in-their-career?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:06:09.124Z"),
    "question" : "What are the certifications that can help PGDM students to make a growth in their career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603695cb0c817f0398facd24"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-a-career-in-product-and-brand-management-in-the-FMCG-sector-for-a-PGDM-fresher?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:07:07.861Z"),
    "question" : "How is a career in product and brand management in the FMCG sector for a PGDM fresher? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036961f0c817f0398facdfc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-start-a-career-as-a-financial-analyst-being-a-non-commerce-graduate-pursuing-a-part-time-PGDM-in-finance?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the easiest route to becoming a financial analyst in Canada?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:08:31.933Z"),
    "question" : "How can I start a career as a financial analyst being a non-commerce graduate pursuing a part-time PGDM in finance? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036964d0c817f0398face94"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-a-career-in-marketing-after-doing-a-PGDM-from-top-B-schools-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Sabit Rawat 1",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:09:17.412Z"),
    "question" : "How good is a career in marketing after doing a PGDM from top B-schools in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603696610c817f0398faceb6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-did-you-convince-yourself-in-believing-that-sports-management-is-the-career-path-you-need-to-take-and-not-any-other-which-your-PGDM-college-offered?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:09:37.794Z"),
    "question" : "How did you convince yourself in believing that sports management is the career path you need to take and not any other which your PGDM college offered? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603696fb0c817f0398fad0af"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-PGDM-in-LLB-add-any-value-with-a-management-degree-in-career-switching?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:12:11.920Z"),
    "question" : "Does PGDM in LLB add any value with a management degree in career switching? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603697130c817f0398fad0f2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-the-IIIT-B-data-science-PGDM-during-a-career-break-with-8-years-of-experience-allowed?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is it worth doing an MSc in data science from IIIT Bangalore? There are two options, a PGDM in data science and an MSc in data science.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:12:35.797Z"),
    "question" : "Is the IIIT-B data science PGDM during a career break with 8 years of experience allowed? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603697380c817f0398fad189"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-skills-that-a-PGDM-in-finance-student-can-learn-in-20-days-of-holiday-vacation-that-may-leverage-her-career?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:13:12.952Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best skills that a PGDM in finance student can learn in 20 days of holiday vacation that may leverage her career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603697510c817f0398fad1ba"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-Manipal-PGDBS-somewhat-equivalent-to-a-PGDM-in-terms-of-a-banking-career?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:13:37.118Z"),
    "question" : "Is a Manipal PGDBS somewhat equivalent to a PGDM in terms of a banking career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603697660c817f0398fad1e0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-PGDM-program-in-any-IIM-is-helpful-in-the-career-growth-for-a-professional-having-4-years-of-experience-in-IT-industry?-",
    "answer" : "Rajiv Ranjan Nanshu Arora Aditya Nandula",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:13:58.801Z"),
    "question" : "How PGDM program in any IIM is helpful in the career growth for a professional having 4 years of experience in IT industry? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603697be0c817f0398fad31b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-pursue-a-PGDM-degree-in-IIM-Bangalore-with-a-career-gap-of-3-years?-",
    "answer" : "Dear Stranger :-) It will be tough but not totally impossible. You can get an admission as long as you can do the following- Compensate for this gap by other stellar components in your profile- Strong CAT score, great academics score etc.Justify the gap with a valid reasonYou have to, of course, satisfy all the eligibility criteria required for admissions. All the best!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:15:26.389Z"),
    "question" : "Can I pursue a PGDM degree in IIM Bangalore with a career gap of 3 years? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603697ea0c817f0398fad3ba"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-and-job-opportunities-after-successful-completion-of-PGDM-in-healthcare-management?-",
    "answer" : "Anand Kumar  Listed below are five entry-level jobs that can put you on track for a management position. If you are pursuing PGDM course from ITM institute, you will be place in a top most company and aspirants will acquire the great skills and creativity. Medical Office Administrator.Medical Executive Assistant.Healthcare Human Resources Manager.Health Information.Social and Community Service Manager.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:16:10.229Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career and job opportunities after successful completion of PGDM in healthcare management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6036980e0c817f0398fad3f8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-can-you-study-beyond-PGDM-to-enhace-your-career-growth-options?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:16:46.440Z"),
    "question" : "What can you study beyond PGDM to enhace your career growth options? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603698560c817f0398fad4d5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/I-want-to-start-my-career-in-credit-analyst-so-which-PGDM-course-will-be-covered-credit-analyst?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:17:58.145Z"),
    "question" : "I want to start my career in credit analyst so which PGDM course will be covered credit analyst? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603698fa0c817f0398fad715"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-entrepreneur-development-career-opportunities-after-doing-a-two-year-PGDM-course?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Sarala Krishnamurthy",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:20:42.458Z"),
    "question" : "What are the entrepreneur development career opportunities after doing a two-year PGDM course? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603699480c817f0398fad85c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-establish-my-career-in-the-operations-industry-after-completing-a-PGDM-in-operations?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:22:00.862Z"),
    "question" : "How can I establish my career in the operations industry after completing a PGDM in operations? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603699620c817f0398fad88e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-way-to-get-a-career-in-a-logistics-company-after-the-PGDM-in-LIVE-Loyola-logistics-and-supply-chain-management?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:22:26.930Z"),
    "question" : "What is the way to get a career in a logistics company after the PGDM in LIVE Loyola logistics and supply chain management? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("603699930c817f0398fad93e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-chances-of-progress-in-the-career-of-an-IT-professional-after-doing-a-hybrid-PGDM-from-Welingkar?-",
    "answer" : "Well, I am not aware of this particular course, Pg Hybrid. But assuming this is a part-time program, this would be enough to make up for the requirement at certain organizations to push you through the next level of hierarchy. A part-time becomes a full time worthy thing, once you work in the management side of things for 3–5 years, and then people hardly notice if you have a full time or part time certificate. Especially if you are doing it from colleges like Welingkar. IT industry is fairly transparent and hence if you make the cut for things in your career,you are well off. Unlike other industries, a part-tim e certificate and proven skill sets would be good enough for you to move up the ladder. Cheers!!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:23:15.230Z"),
    "question" : "What are the chances of progress in the career of an IT professional after doing a hybrid PGDM from Welingkar? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60369a4f0c817f0398fadb96"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-course-can-I-opt-for-after-a-PGDM-as-a-working-professional-which-can-help-in-my-career-growth?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which is the best course in an MBA and does that course have any scope in the future?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:26:23.652Z"),
    "question" : "What course can I opt for after a PGDM as a working professional which can help in my career growth? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("60369b610c817f0398fadf0e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-career-scope-and-average-salary-if-I-choose-a-PGDM-dual-specialization-in-marketing-and-international-business?-",
    "answer" : "",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-24T18:30:57.703Z"),
    "question" : "What are the career scope and average salary if I choose a PGDM dual specialization in marketing and international business? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
